Translated by Releska
The sky of the blue-and-white sky
The sky of the blue sky
With the idea of an Antrag
it aims for a short phase
to take off my identity
as if I have always been at the other class
I know I don't play any game
but sometimes I guess I'll play a lot
so, yeah happy
Without you, I don't look like a good
Out edge, the washroom
For a long time, we've got a picture of you
When you and you and you
If you want to meet me
With the speed of life, I can't give up
Because it's so exciting
I do not want to lose, but I know I'll be in trouble!
I want to play again!
I'll be in trouble with the sky!
No, I can't. It's a big thing that I've been thinking since a long time ago.
True. I learned a lot, so I thought it was going to be a good deal.
What? You're getting a little sleepy.
I can feel the tension from now on.
Hey, Muka, you know?
I don't know.
Wait!
I'm coming.
Oh, return.
Muka, Muka, what's wrong with that face?
We were talking to each other like this.
Shibelia said she saw it, but...
She was flying from the second floor.
What? She was flying?
That's right.
She was flying from the second floor to the third floor.
Is it a fish?
That's not it?
She was flying from the third floor to the third floor to the third floor.
She was flying from the seventh floor to the seventh floor.
Stop it!
I'm so sorry.
What are you thinking about?
I've been wanting to buy a new one today.
Oh no!
Look! She's flying from the third floor to the fifth floor.
That's why I'm flying from the second floor to the seventh floor.
I wonder if she's flying from the second floor to the third floor.
That's weird.
Why is she flying from the third floor to the seventh floor?
That's...
I don't want to fly the sky.
What?
I see.
You want to fly?
That's nonsense!
You can't fly.
I'm not going to fly.
Who did you decide?
Huh?
Why?
I know who you are.
I'm feeling it.
I see.
I'm going to fly too.
What is that?
It's a human plane that I made before.
A human plane?
It's amazing.
Can I fly with this?
I can fly with this.
Huh?
What?
I made it before?
I didn't fly with this.
But I'm not going to fly.
How is it?
Are you ready?
Huh?
I'm going to fly.
If I try to fly with this, I can fly.
But...
I'm going to fly.
I'm going to fly too.
That's why I'm going to fly.
If you don't mind, you'll have to fly.
That's right, right?
You're going to fly.
If you don't mind, you'll have to fly.
I can fly.
Yeah.
I'll try.
Hey, there are a lot of things.
You look like you're going to fly.
Yeah.
Did you know there was something like this?
It's amazing.
Well, I wanted to tell you.
I told you about it.
I saw it in elementary school.
Yeah, I like it.
I think it's this one.
What?
I think it's fun.
But it's a human-like airplane.
A human-like airplane?
What is that?
A friendly sport?
I didn't hear it.
I want to know.
Why don't you give it to me?
Hey, hey.
Why do you look like a human-like airplane?
The five-year-old is over today.
I can't do anything about it, but...
I don't know what to do.
If you know it, you're going to die.
Oh, I see.
It's like a ghost.
Huh?
You're not going to lie.
I'm going to show you my life.
Shut up!
I'm not going to lie.
I'm going to answer your questions.
I'm not going to lie to you.
I'm going to fly.
I want to fly to the sky.
The sky?
I want to fly?
Oh, okay.
You were beautiful.
Oh, I was EXPOLThis.
Yeah.
I'll show you!
Well, I can't make butter sauce out of this.
Isn't the ingredients after all?
Yeah.
I know what you're saying.
It seems I can not still do anything.
Hey, Ayurthra!
It's over now.
I did it!
Ah! I like it! It's here!
All right, now, let's go!
Yeah!
Let's go!
Woohoo!
Hey!
I'm not good at anything.
I just got a lot of money from the government.
How could I do that?
That was a waste of money for selling.
What are you doing with me?
I'm using a trash can.
What?
A trash can?
I'm just using a trash can.
But I thought I'd use this trash can.
Maybe it's really a trash can.
I don't think so.
I really didn't think so.
I-I don't know.
I'm going to fly, I'm going to fly!
I like it, isn't it?
If it's possible, I might not be able to fly.
Huh?
I noticed a big problem.
What do you mean by that?
Oh, my legs hurt.
What?
I think this is a very fatal problem.
I'll get ready for it.
Huh?
Is it like a red light on your face?
Yeah.
It's because it's on your face, isn't it?
That's...
It's a little scary, but...
Well, isn't that right?
Yeah, I'll do that.
I'll do that.
Wow!
Is there really something?
Well, Muka Muka-chan!
I'm going to fly!
Lanka, I know you're going to fly from the ceiling to the ceiling.
I know, but I'll fly with you when I'm flying.
That's the problem!
I'm going to fly, isn't it?
If you have a flight to the front,
you can fly like that.
I'm going to fly, okay?
Okay, then Muka Muka-chan!
I'm going to fly with a nice flying food!
Wow!
Why don't you fight again?
Muka Muka is too heavy.
That's...
Maybe now?
Muka Muka!
I want to fly!
I'm flying!
The End
Muka Muka!
Muka Muka! Are you sure?
I was about to cry, I was about to cry.
Is Muka Muka happy?
Yes, I'm happy that Muka Muka wants to eat Sora.
Muka Muka can't eat Muka Muka like this.
What are you talking about? It's more like a human being.
I don't know if I want to eat it.
I don't want to eat it. I don't want to eat it at all.
I don't want to eat it at all.
Let's go.
I...
I want to eat it too.
Muka Muka can't eat Muka Muka like this.
Let's do it.
Ah! The weather is coming tomorrow.
I'm going to sleep.
Akira!
Wait!
Let's do it.
I'm going to sleep tomorrow.
I'm going to sleep.
Where?
It's right. The captain and the Yamata are right there.
I'm going to sleep.
Why? Why are you doing this to Muka?
I'm going to make something like this.
It's not a fairing.
Fairing?
Oh, it's a place where I'm finally here.
Take it.
The treasure of the treasure!
I'm going to sleep!
Yes.
Let's do it!
Who do I get ready?
Renka! You must have a lot of basic sunglasses!
But I want to take them out in front of Renka's sunglasses!
That's right!
I'll get some real thunderbolt laser.
Ah...
What... What are you doing?
I'll never lose to anyone like you!
Understood.
Here, here, right here, right?
Here, here, right here.
Muhua!
I am...
Ta-da!
Change, time to do it!
I wonder if I could go again.
Listen to me. I've got a tomorrow as well.
Yeah. I've got a tomorrow as well.
Yeah, I've got a tomorrow as well.
If you are a bread rider,
to be honest, you can choose a right path of yourself
to travel alone and travel alone.
Select and travel alone.
Who are you looking at?
You've been dreaming of a child, haven't you?
That dream will come true.
Doctor.
I'm sorry about this.
Why did you say that?
Did something happen to you?
What's wrong?
You don't feel well.
But you don't feel well?
What's wrong with you, Doctor?
What's wrong with you?
Tell me!
That's what I'm thinking about.
What?
I don't want anyone to tell me.
What's wrong?
I'll stop it!
If I were you, I wouldn't know how to make myself.
That's why I can't tell you.
I can't tell you.
You've been dreaming of a child.
That's wrong.
What's wrong?
That's...
Mom, you're so annoying.
You're not angry at all.
Let's do it one more time.
Don't give up on it.
But...
Let's have a good day.
It's not time to waste.
What's wrong?
I can't tell you.
Don't give up.
It's not time to waste.
What's wrong?
That's right.
This is a good deal.
Oh no!
The intro of the game is about to start!
I won't do anything!
What will be the first round?
Guess the second round is almost the last round!
But...
Okay, then, let's get started.
This place is quite a lot.
I'm going to see my new partner, Yasunoute.
I'm so embarrassed!
Yasunoute is really dazzled!
Huh? I always admired you!
You're right!
The signal's 5.3rd orange.
Roger!
You're working hard for me!
Uh-oh!
Huh?
Gankan! Gankan!
Don't do this to me!
I'm sorry! Don't do this to me!
It's time for the final round.
Let's move on to the next team.
I'll do it!
Please get close to me!
It's time for the final round!
Don't do this to me!
I'll do it!
It's time for the final round!
I'm sorry!
I was just dreaming.
I'm not capable of anything!
You're good.
I'm not!
It's time for the final round.
Hey, Yuma, I'm gonna show you one.
Huh?
You think this is poison?
Is there poison on my head?
I found this poison in my cash register.
This call is after the count of 10.
It's about 10 o'clock in the morning.
Why? Why didn't you tell me where I was?
That's probably because Uiba wanted to make a dream in Uiba's hands.
A dream?
Oh my god!
What's going on?
It's so hot!
I don't think I want to take the sky away from anyone.
I don't want to give up.
That's why I want to take it away.
If you don't give up, you can't make a dream.
I don't know.
Where are you going?
Wait for me!
To be continued
Ato boyo nori ni no ii aritsu mo iru no
Toki wo koe koko ye kite iru hein
Hein na yatsu watashi taji nani ko iwa tsugetsui jija uta
Beautiful, and the eyes of them are awesome
Boy, boy, boy, boy, boy, boy
Yo yo, so beautiful, so beautiful
I wonder what you'll all travel
I am the one taking the moment to be alone.
Let's be friends!
T comfort
不明, notokunturnia, notokunturnia.
We will have you here.
It's been a while.
You look tired now?
Tachia, you were so good at taking the food.
Don't eat the lentil noodles!
Next time, I will be with you from Ugunmukapara!
I'm still in the market, today!
I'm looking forward to seeing you again!